A Guide to the Allen Caperton Braxton Papers
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #3329
Allen Caperton Braxton Papers
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
3329
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was purchased September 30, 1949.
Container List
- PAPERS OF ALLEN CAPERTON BRAXTON
  - Legal Correspondence:
    - Braxton Correspondence: A-Z, 1887; (4 folders) (Box Box 1)
    - Braxton Correspondence: A-E, 1896 (Box Box 1)
    - Braxton Correspondence: F-Z, 1896; (4 folders) (Box Box 2)
    - Braxton Correspondence, 1901-1902 (Box Box 3.)
    - Braxton Correspondence: A-E, 1904; (4 folders) (Box Box 3.)
    - Braxton Correspondence: F-L, 1904; (4 folders) (Box Box 4)
    - Braxton Correspondence: M-Z, 1904; (5 folders) (Box Box 5)
    - Braxton Correspondence: A-Z, 1905; (5 folders) (Box Box 6)
  - Legal Accounts:
    - Braxton Accounts: A-V, 1887-1898; (5 folders) (Box Box 7)
    - Braxton Accounts: W-Z, 1887-1898 (Box Box 8)
    - Braxton Accounts: A-Z, 1903-1905; (3 folders) (Box Box 8)
  - Legal and Miscellaneous Papers:
    - Braxton Legal and Miscellaneous Papers, 1886-1902, n.d.; (2 folders) (Box Box 8)
    - Braxton Legal Papers: Pamphlets on constitutional articles on Corporate Commission, Elective Franchise, and Suffrage, 1897-1902; (1 of 2) (Box Box 8)
    - Braxton Legal Papers: Pamphlets on constitutional articles on Corporate Commission, Elective Franchise, and Suffrage, 1897-1902; (2 of 2) (Box Box 9)
    - Braxton Legal Papers: Proposed constitutional articles on Corporations, 1901, n.d.; (2 folders) (Box Box 9)
    - Braxton Legal Papers: Proposed consitutional articles on Corporations--Notes, 1902, n.d. (Box Box 9)
- PAPERS OF HENRY W. HOLT
  - Legal Correspondence:
    - Holt Correspondence: A-Z, 1908-1912; (5 folders) (Box Box 10)
    - Holt Correspondence: A-H, 1916 (Box Box 10)
    - Holt Correspondence: Hu-Z, 1916; (2 folders) (Box Box 11)
    - Holt Correspondence: A-Z, 1917; (3 folders) (Box Box 11)
    - Holt Correspondence: A-Z, 1918 (Box Box 11)
    - Holt Correspondence: A-Z, 1922 (Box Box 12)
    - Holt Correspondence: A-Z, 1946-1947; (3 folders) (Box Box 12)
  - Legal Accounts:
    - Holt Accounts: A-N, 1920-1925; (3 folders) (Box Box 12)
    - Holt Accounts: P-Z, 1920-1925; (3 folders) (Box Box 13)
    - Holt Accounts: A-S, 1930-1933; (3 folders) (Box Box 13)
    - Holt Accounts: S-W, 1930-1933; (3 folders) (Box Box 14)
    - Holt Accounts: A-T, 1934-1936; (3 folders) (Box Box 14)
    - Holt Accounts: T-Z, 1934-1936; (2 folders) (Box Box 15)
    - Holt Accounts: A-Z, 1945-1947; (3 folders) (Box Box 15)
  - Legal and Miscellaneous Papers:
    - Holt Legal and Miscellaneous Papers, 1905-1917 (Box Box 16)
    - Holt Legal and Miscellaneous Papers, 1938-1947 (Box Box 16)
    - War Industries Board: Printed, 1918-1919 (Box Box 16)
    - War Industries Board: Reports, 1918 (Box Box 16)
- PAPERS OF W. R. TYREE COMPANY
  - Business Correspondence:
    - W. R. Tyree Business Correspondence: A-P, 1888; (2 folders) (Box Box 16)
    - W. R. Tyree Business Correspondence: Q-T, 1888 (Box Box 17)
    - W. R. Tyree Business Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1888 (Box Box 17)
    - W. R. Tyree Accounts: A-Z, 1888; (3 folders) (Box Box 17)